[{"answer": "In such a large-scale systemic way, no, I've been at the fall of President Mobutu in Zaire that's now Congo when, you know, soldiers were -- who haven't been paid were running riots and beating up reporters and grabbing cameras.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Have you ever known the collective media come under such an attack?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, it's a continuation of what we saw very abruptly really in the early morning hours Wednesday.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What kind of activities are now going on against these protesters by pro-Mubarak forces tonight from what you can gather?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard to predict, you know, what -- I mean the next few hours will hold.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What's your thoughts on this?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, he's very capable, very bright, a lot of experience in intelligence matters and in matters that are more military and security in nature.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What kind of guy is he?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's not just a misreading of what happened on the ground but I think it indicates sometimes what happens to leaders when they're -- when they're not observing what is plainly evident.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What was your take on that?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "No offense to the two fine reporters from \"The New York Times\" that wrote that report, Piers, and they do have some new information in there, but the basic thrust of it is something we've been reporting since Tuesday afternoon.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Is this actually new or has this been the -- the sort of plan below ground that's been going all the time?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "It is and there are people watching out there who are fans of Senator McCain and there are some who are critics of Senator McCain, because he's been so active in politics in recent years including being President Obama's opponent.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Is that your reading of what's going on here, John?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "No, this is a concerted effort and campaign to intimidate -- intimidate and confiscate equipment and it's having an effect.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like quite like this against the media?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "This is serious stuff, isn't it?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to say.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "And Nic, there can't be any doubt now surely that the thugs are acting on the directions of the government, can there?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Today was the first time throughout the past 10 days that I feel actually scared closer to Tahrir.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "What's been your experience as a journalist trying to get your story out there?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I'm definitely afraid even to drive through the city.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Do you feel the thugs have now got control of the streets?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "As long as I can, there's no -- the situation is very unpredictability.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Sarah, how long do you think you can continue to use Twitter, to use your computer to try and get information out to the west?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, he's coming to the end of his term.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What do you think is really going on here?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's horrible violence.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "When you see journalists being beaten, stabbed, kidnapped, threatened with beheadings, what's your view of that?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "If they accept it, if the army accepts it and if Suleiman is willing to do it and if Mubarak is willing to give him that blessing, yes.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Do you think that is a credible plan that's going to work?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "When you see the growing violence between the two factions, that's not going to get better, is it?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "The mood is very sober, very skeptical, skeptical of -- and skeptical of the United States' power in this situation.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What is the mood like in Israel about what's going on in Egypt?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Well, frankly, I thought that you guys were and women were engaging in a little professional narcissism.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What is your take on the aggression towards the media?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think they're very dangerous at all, piers.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "In your expert opinion how extremist are they, how dangerous are they?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, part of the -- why I think that's quite unlikely is these Egyptian militant groups that killed more than a thousand Egyptians in the '90s and culminating with a horrific massacre in Luxor in '97 where a group of militants went hunting tourists from -- in the Luxor ruins motoring more than 50 of them, these are kind of activities really destroyed the group of these militant groups in Egypt.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "So even though there's no link at the moment, is there not an increasing danger that there might be?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "ERGEN: You know, Piers, it could become the next Afghanistan.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What's your view of the Yemen?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Will that convince him to step down?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Oh, they're widely popular.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Nic, how popular do you think this judge's sentiments are?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "We really don't know what could happen next.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Ivan, what is the state of tension there, because we keep hearing that the reason the media is being brutalized is because of fears there may be something appalling about to go down?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "When we spoke this time last night, I was much more afraid, really, because I had no idea.", "docId": "110203pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Ivan, do you feel apprehensive about your own safety there?", "qSentId": 447}]